Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Braving the Maze
Episode 7
These colorful Bulala are so beautiful.
It seems to be born from these plants
Why did they all come together suddenly?
Do they want to stick with me?
It’s so
numbing!
You must remember that these Bulalas are dangerous
The gray Bulala, you will be electrocuted if you touch it.
The different colors of Bulala produced here have different characteristics.
And little Bulala will be attracted to ones of the same color
When gathered together, they will become larger
So that little gray Bulala
Only then did it fly to Wolffy.
He even ate it
No matter what, please avoid it
Got it?
Got it now
Let’s keep going
Everyone, hurry up. It’s very windy here.
It’s too hard to hide while walking
What is this? Why always blocking the road? Get out of my way.
It turns out that you can pass like this
These flowers don’t look dangerous, so let me charge first.
So itchy
I won
It smells so spicy
Wolffy, what about
I’m not a quitter.
Go ahead
We’re out thanks to Wolffy
It feels a little strange here
I won’t go first this time
I’ll go first this time
This is the paint on the tree
Slowy, is there any news about my Wolffy?
Not yet. But I have sent drones into the rifts to search.
In addition, I also set up surveillance cameras around the rifts.
An alarm will sound whenever there is any movement
The alarm is coming soon
What is that? So fast
The alarm went off. What happened?
I’ll investigate and analyze it right now. I’ll tell you the news right away.
Slowy
No, I have to go to Goats’ Village.
Please wake up, Weslie
What happened to me just now
You were the one who opened the way, but then you suddenly started dancing
I guess it’s the sap that makes people dance.
Anyway, don’t touch anything with wicker
Then let’s squat and walk
It’s okay, just a little tired
not good
Why am I here?
Wolffy Weslie
where are you
Why are we back here again?
Now I realize that they look exactly the same everywhere.
lost
What should I do? It’s so scary here.
where did everyone go
Where are they?
Mommy, is Daddy back?
I don’t know yet, so let’s go to Goats’ Village now to see what’s going on.
What a beautiful stone
Son, follow quickly
Mommy, look at this stone
go away
what is that
Let’s run quickly
Is anyone there?
Finally found someone
Let it go
I don’t want to go alone anymore. It’s too scary.
Okay, let’s go together
But what should we do if we are separated again?
That’ll be no problem
Let’s go quickly
Why don’t you try to explain to him that you didn’t abandon him back then?
Sparky
In fact, back then
This is a Teardrop Bulala. If we touch it, it will make our whole body wet and heavy.
Moving will also become difficult
thank you for saving me
stop talking
Let’s walk carefully next
Oops, the weird Bulala is here again
Then go quickly
Why is there one in front?
It’s getting closer here too
Darn we’re surrounded
Sparky, let’s go here
Weslie
By the way just now
You wait for me
I’ll wait for you
Sparky, come back soon
I’m back
Sparky
Since it is fire
Then use water to deal with it
Come out quickly
Let’s go quickly
what this tree looks like
I always feel like this place is familiar
who
Wolffy
Are you okay Wolffy
fine
have you found a way out
No. every place looks the same
like a maze
Do you think these trees look like trees around your house?
Indeed, it looks exactly like the forest outside my house.
follow me
Just find these trees with weird postures
Follow their longest branches
See it
Wilie and I used to pick mushrooms in the forest and play hide-and-seek.
I’m very familiar with this terrain.
I’ll go bring them out
Which side is Goats’ Village?
Mommy, go this way
I didn’t expect that my son, you have such a good sense of direction.
Thanks to Daddy, he often comes to take me to play hide-and-seek and pick mushrooms
I know the way
Run quickly
Sparky, actually I didn’t leave you behind back then
I’m really trying to think of a way to save you
In fact, I always believed in you back then
Until you said that to me
I won’t look for you again in the future
Because you sealed the hole we dug together
Didn’t you seal that hole?
No, I think the hole is sealed
That’s why I thought you were blaming me
Who sealed that hole?
Reporting to Your Majesty, we have just uncovered an assassin’s plan.
assassin
The cave was sealed by Keyan and Ketian
It turned out to be a misunderstanding
this
That
You are here
The exit is over here. Come with me.
That
Let’s keep moving forward
I remember that Wolffy often came to the gate to catch us.
Every time Weslie stepped forward and beat him away
I don’t know where they are now
That’s Wolnie and Wilie
They are running this way
where
To be continued